Hey!
那個
when we are filming
攝影
Later
我們待會啊
I want the color temperature of this scene, to have a twilight look.
這邊的色溫我想要拍那種黃昏的感覺
OK.
好
Then
然後
the lead actress will walk through here.
待會女主從這邊走過來的時候啊
From her hip line to her legs
從她的那個臀線到她的腿
Make sure you shoot it beautifully for me.
幫我拍漂亮一點
Pan up like this.
這樣帶上去
Just pan up from the bottom like this.
就從下這樣往上帶
YES! Yes!
對對對對對
OK
OK
Thank you very much.
好麻煩妳了
Hey!
那個
How are the male actors doing are they done getting ready?
男演員準備的如何了
They are all OK.
都OK了
Okay, good.
OK吼好
Can you…
可以
luchboxes there
那那個便當
past them out to everyone
待會麻煩把它發一發
And remember to give it to anyone who hasn't eaten yet.
記得看誰沒吃要記得給他哦
OK.
好
ok
ok
Director sir
大導演
How's the setup coming along?
準備的如何呀
Ahh… It's
那我
my first time shooting an adult movie.
第一次拍攝AV啊
So I'm hoping it'll be the same as the scenes that I have pictured in my head.
所以我希望能跟我腦中的畫面一樣
but
只是
I'm not so sure.
我沒有把握
as long as it sells, it's all good
能賣座就是了
It's my big break
好不容易才得來的機會
It took me a long time to convince my dad.
我可是說服我爸很久
That's why he let you shoot it.
才讓你拍攝的
When you were a kid, didn't you say you wanted to win an Oscar?
你小時候不是還說要拿奧斯卡
Where's your confidence at?
你自信呢
okay, alright
好啦
I'll do my best. I'll do my best.
我努力我努力
It seems like my role is an agent for today.
我今天算是經紀
This is Bebe Mong.
這是孟若羽
She is very famous.
鼎鼎大名
Have you heard of her?
有聽過吧
Yes, I have
有啊
It's an honor to meet you.
久仰久仰
Hello Heh Heh (giggles)
妳好呵呵
Hello Hi
妳好妳好
Hello, I'm Cici, today's producer.
你們好我是今天的製片筱希
This way to makeup and wardrobe, please.
那我們演員梳化這邊請
Ok no problem
哎呦沒事啦
She is
人家
Candy and is really experienced.
若羽經驗超級豐富
She is the best in porno industry.
行業中的翹楚
It's really okay.
真的沒事啦
Good luck
加油
OK.
好
Boss
經理
You're so busy today.
你今天很忙哦
you've been ignoring me all day.
一整天都不理人家
I've got more work than usual today.
今天工作比較多啊
I've been so dripping wet all day.
人家今天濕噠噠一整天了
You didn't pay any attention and ignored me all day.
你都不理人家
It made me so horny and I wanted it so bad.
害人家很想要
This panties
這內褲
It's perfect for you.
也太適合妳了吧
Do you like it?
喜歡嗎
Yes, I do.
喜歡
OK.
好
Cut
卡
OK
OK
That was good
這個可以
tale slate
尾板
2 of 3
2之3
take one
take one
OK
OK
Okay, let's come in and shoot from that angle.
好來那那個攝影我們鏡位進去
OK.
好
Good great
好很好
That was a good one.
剛剛這個不錯哦
Okay, let's change angles.
好我們換個鏡位
And later when we shoot
那待會攝影的部分
capture for me more of the actress's face.
幫我把那個女演員的臉多帶一點
And let me know if the angle looks good.
然後鏡位好的話就跟我說一聲
okay give me a minute.
好等我一下喔
OK
OK
OK.
好
Does the angle work and look good?
鏡位OK了齁
Let's get the cast ready.
來演員準備
okay
好囉
come
來
let's continue
繼續哦來
You have such a hot body.
這麼好的身材
It's been a long day at work today.
今天工作一整天
Bring up the angle a little more, please
來鏡位再幫我往上帶一點對
You ignored me all day today.
你今天都不理人家
I thought you were bored of me already.
害我以為你對我膩了
How could I be?
怎麼會
I'm here right now, aren't I?
現在我不就來了嗎
Ok cut
好來卡
Come here, let's make a little adjustments.
來這邊我們調整一下
tale slate
尾板
take two
take two
OK.
好
Alright, let's have the male actors come here
來我們男演員啊
pay attention to what's happening on this side.
注意一下剛這邊啊
Because your character is set up to express your lust.
因為你的人設上是要展現你的欲望
A lust you haven't felt for a long time is getting ready to explode.
很久沒有的欲望要這樣出來
OK
OK
Alright, you take a step back.
好來你退一步
and we'll show you how we want the scene done
然後我們來試一次給你看齁
from here where the actress was just at
在剛剛女演員這個地方啊
When we pan to the waist area
我們走到腰的位置的時候
You're going to have to move in quickly
你要極快迅速的來一次上
That’s it
對
Also the look on your face should
然後到臉這個部分
show how much you want her
很想要她
And then go straight down.
然後直接往下走啊
when you get to the legs
到腿的這個時候呢
slowly tilt and pan the camera to show how silky smooth her skin is.
再慢慢的體驗她絲滑的觸感肌膚
OK
OK
Like this
這樣子
Do you understand?
可以瞭解嗎
got it I understand.
好瞭解
Okay, one more thing
好那我們再一個喔
camera man
來攝影
come here
這邊
later when you shoot do more close-ups
待會特寫鏡頭再多一點
OK
OK
OK.
好
Okay ok let's go.
好好來
Then let's continue.
那我們繼續
let's get ready
來準備哦
good, very good
好很好喔
Let's go, guys!
大家加油
We're almost done.
快快結束了
we're almost done guys
快結束了好
Alright, let's get ready.
好來準備囉
I can't stand it
受不了了
Hey director
欸導演
I can't
不行啦
I just can't get it up
沒辦法啦
what's wrong?
怎麼樣
You still can't get it up.
還是不行哦
There's really nothing I can do.
真的沒辦法啦
Director
導演
The time frame is a little too tight.
那個時間有點緊
We need to hurry
要快點
okay, ok
好好
I know, I know.
知道了知道了
OK.
好
We can't afford to spend any more time and money.
我們不可能再花另外的時間跟金錢
to shoot it again.
再重拍一次
How can I tell my father we need to reshoot this?
你這樣我要怎麼跟我爸交代
This….
這
Don't just stand there.
你不要杵在那邊啊
Hurry up and figure something out
趕緊快想想辦法
You're the one that hired everyone
人也是你找的
What is wrong with you?
狀態怎麼那麼差
This.
這個
This is the first time this ever happend
我也是第一次遇到這個狀況啊
okay, alright
好啦
Let me figure something out
我會再想想
Director sir
大導演
I have an idea.
我有個想法
You, yourself probably have very good stamina.
你體力應該不錯吧
and you're the only one here who can act.
在場就你會演戲
so
要不
you should replace him
你來演
It's just fucking isn't it?
不就做個愛嘛
Bebe
若羽
Director
導演
I don't mind
我可以啊
You're joking, right?
這開玩笑的吧
I
我
What! Me!
我耶
When you were a kid, I saw you naked in the bath.
小時候洗澡的時候都嘛看光光了
You don't have any confidence in yourself
你是對自己沒自信
or do you have any other bright ideas?
還是你有更好的辦法
This….
這
This.
這個
do it?
有可能嗎
Director…..
導演那
then I'll leave you to it.
就麻煩你了啊
come
來
everyone
大家
How about we get a POV angle, first person view?
我們弄個POV第一人稱視角如何
Like this
這樣子
without showing your face
不露臉
Bobby do you have any comments.
陳博你也沒有意見吧
Our Bebe is so hot and beautiful.
我們家若羽那麼漂亮
This….
這
I'll try my best
我我努力看看
Okay
好吧
then…. (in that case)
那
Then I'll start.
那我開始囉
Okay
好啊
You can touch them.
可以摸啊
they're so big
好大
Do you like it?
喜歡嗎
Yes, I do.
喜歡
I like it very much!
太喜歡了
It's feels so good
好舒服哦
You're so horny
你這樣好色哦